[Music]
ah
you taste like
cigarettes I hat it every chance I
get girl you got me tripping
sweat you pull me back every time I quit
yeah you taste like
cigarettes your body feels like
disrespect let you play me like an
instrument but I'm addicted to it yeah
I'm addicted to it yeah yeah I felt your
coming and I couldn't
escape I'm in a belly of the Beast again
my dirty secret that keeps me awake
don't stop now you got me ready to blow
[Applause]
[Music]
you tast my
cigarettes I got a problem think I'm
into
it I breather in and hold it in my chest
I take a hit and let it bur my lip
burn my lips hey I felt you coming and I
couldn't
escape I'm made a belly of the Beast
again my dirty secret that keeps me
awake don't stop now you got me ready to
[Applause]
[Music]
you got me blow it
away I do
[Music]
anything tell me what to do
o Hey trco trco where's the St
passed out in the back of my
car down from night
before how we let it get this
[Music]